走开
Get the fuck off me.
你怎么知道没办法救她
How do you know that there's no way to save her?
你不是上帝
You're not God!
内森
Nathan!
就是你害了她
You're just the one who's killing her!
让她在这等着我*
*Tell her to wait right here for me
我想尽快回来*
*I'll try to get right back
现在我就只能看到她的拒绝*
*Right now her no is all I see
像是活在陷阱里一样*
*Like living in a trap
告诉她我需要自己一个人静一静*
*Tell her I need some time alone
花点时间理清头绪*
*Some time to work things out
告诉她等我回到家*
*Tell her when I come back home
我会把我们过去的快乐时光带回来*
*I'll bring our good times back
我明白*
*I get it
你是认真的*
*You meant it
没关系  我们不会后悔*
*That's cool, we'll never regret it
在悲伤中我们已度过了风暴*
*By morning this storm had moved on
毫无预警*
*Gave me no warning
一切都会好起来*
*It's gonna be all right
只需要一晚安宁*
*Oh, but it's gonna take all night
一切都会好起来*
*It's gonna be okay
今天就会出现转机*
Today is not that day
我们怎么停下来了
Uh, why have we stopped?
有种奇怪的生物叫做人类
There's these weird things called human beings
我们时不时会饿
and we get hungry at lunch time.
这  就这个破地方
Here, this shithole?
算了  我这次就算了
Yeah, no thanks, I'll sit this one out.
爸爸让你
Dad said be inside
五分钟之内进去
in five minutes.
把门关上
Hey, close the door!
这样多好
How nice is this?
我们三个一块出来公路旅行
Three of us on the open road.
我们三个
There's three of us?
态度好点
Be nice.
爸  她讨厌我们
Dad, she hates us.
他不讨厌我们
She does not hate us.
她就是到了叛逆期了
She's just a teenager.
该到了不听话的时候了
Kind of goes with the territory.
等你到了她那个年纪你就明白了
You'll understand one day when you're her age.
如果我那么反复无常就杀了我吧
Kill me if I ever get that moody.
我发誓你们俩
I swear you two
天差地别
couldn't be more different,
但是你们都像你们的妈妈
and yet you're both just like your mama.
她肯定会喜欢一起出来旅行的
She would have loved this.
爸
Dad?
怎么了
Huh?
我不希望你死
I don't want you to die.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
要是出了什么坏事呢
What if something bad happens?
不会出什么坏事
Nothing bad is gonna happen.
我保证
I promise.
拉勾勾
Pinky swear?
来吧
Come on.
需要加满吗
Would you like me to top it off?
安静
Be quiet.
心灵感应需要精神高度集中
Psychic powers require maximum focus.
你举着
You're holding up...
三根手指
Three fingers!
错了
Wrong.
- 你作弊  - 你才作弊
\ You cheated! \ You cheated!
你之前举着三根然后放下来了一根
You had three fingers and you put one down.
你是怎么知道的
How do you know that?
那意味着你透过手指缝
That means you were peeking
偷看了
through the fingers then.
我没偷看
I was not peeking through my fingers.
- 那你是怎么知道的  - 你变手了
- Then how did you know? - You switched it.
你怎么知道  你能心灵感应
How do you know, are you psychic?
你是说你真的能读心
So you're saying that you're actually a psychic.
也许就是呢  没准就是这样
Maybe I am, maybe I am.
那我需要知道
All right, then I need to know
这周末的比赛谁会赢
who's gonna win the game this weekend.
- 给你  亲爱的  - 谢谢
- Here you go, honey. - Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
你确定什么都不要
You sure you don't want anything?
- 不要  - 不来点煎饼吗
\ Nope. \ Want some pancakes?
不了  我不饿
Nope, I'm not hungry.
你还好吗
You feel okay?
没事
Yup.
你到底还吃不吃兼并了
You gonna have any pancake
还是说
with your syrup, or you're just...
你打算直接喝糖浆
gonna go straight liquid?
别说我
Don't judge me.
我喜欢糖浆
I like syrup.
用不用我给你把盖子拧开
Do you just want me to take the lid off
好让你直接倒出来
so you can just pour it all directly straight on there?
那样还容易点
Might be easier.
怎么了
What?
你担心有人偷车吗
Uh, are you afraid someone's gonna steal it?
怎么了  你担心了吗  茜茜
Why, does it bother you, Sissy?
首先  内森
Firstly, Nathan,
你能不能别叫我茜茜了  我又不是小孩子了
can you not call me "Sissy" because I'm not seven.
你就不能在父亲节叫他爸吗
Can't you call him "Dad" even on Father's Day?
你还记得
Hey, you remembered!
你给我准备了什么
All right, what'd you get me?
一个大大的拥抱
A super big hug.
起开
Get out of here.
- 你想要拥抱吗  - 天呐
- You want a hug? - Oh my God.
你  别过来
You\\ oh\\ no!
你们太奇怪饿了
You guys are so weird.
父亲节快乐
Happy Father's Day.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
瞧
Look at that.
父亲节奶昔
A little Father's Day milkshake.
如你所见
SALESPERSON: As you can see,
我们由很多种类的花座
we have a wide range of receptacles.
你们觉得怎么样  姑娘们
What do you think, girls?
这些丑死了
They're ugly.
我觉得他哪个都不喜欢
I don't think she'd have liked any of them.
她生前有没有特别喜欢的颜色
Is there a particular color that she was fond of?
她一直很喜欢红色
She always loved a good red.
女士
Miss?
不用找了
Keep the change.
你为什么不和我们一起到前面来坐
Why don't you ride up front with us?
我喜欢在后面呆着
I like it back here.
不颠吗
Isn't it bumpy?
你给我带了棉花糖吗
Did you get my marshmallows?
后面安静
It's quiet.
但是不安全
But it's not that safe.
多谢你们的理解
Thank you so much for your understanding.
我觉得这样不合法
I don't think it's legal.
我们尽量不碰到陷坑
We'll try not to hit any potholes!
别闹了
Cut it out!
这里就是  目的地了
So this is the\\ the spot.
别有风味  不是吗
It's really something, isn't it?
这没信号
There's no service.
你打算给我们讲故事吗
Are you gonna tell us the story?
17年前
So, 17 years ago,
我遇到了你们的母亲
when I met your mama,
我们当时沿着现在走的这条路
we took a road trip
进行公路旅行
following the same path we're on now.
一样的加油站  一样的晚餐
Same gas station, same diner.
妈妈吃了煎饼吗
Did Mom have the pancakes?
你知道她吃了
You know she had the pancakes.
我们不知道要去向何方
See, we didn't know where we were goin',
但我们有意如此
and that was kind of the idea.
我们就想行驶在公路上
We just wanted to be on the open road,
享受自由
total freedom.
我们在这里停下
So we stopped here.
一起喝了一瓶葡萄酒
We drank a bottle of wine together.
然后我走到你们母亲身边
And then I walked Mom...
就在克莱尔站的地方
right there where Claire's standing...
我当时都没准备戒指
I didn't have a ring or anything,
但是  我要她嫁给我
but... I asked her to marry me.
所以说
So, no,
当时这个地方确实没什么特别的
there wasn't anything special about this place.
但是现在不一样了
But there is now.
我们就在这里让她安息
And this is where we'll lay her to rest.
都一年过去了
Yeah, about a year late.
好了
All right.
把行李拿下来吧
Let's get unpacked.
小玛  天气有点凉了
Mags, why don't you grab your jacket
你去把你的夹克拿出来
since it's gettin' a little chilly?
把我的也拿出来  好吗
Grab mine too, would you?
亲爱的
Hi baby.
我六点之后
I'm not gonna be back from work
才能回家
till after six,
你能不能帮小玛做点晚餐
so can you please make Maggie some dinner?
冰箱里有通心粉
There's pasta in the fridge.
你只需要热一下就行了
All you have to do is iterally just heat it up.
我在睡觉前就回来了
Um, I will be back for bedtime.
爸爸会先回去  但是你也知道他的厨艺
Dad'll be home, but you know what his cooking is like.
And...还有
昨晚的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about last night.
那场架吵的毫无意义
That was a stupid fight.
我知道你爱我
I know you love me.
我也爱你
And I love you.
得走了
Okay, I gotta go.
我爱你  亲爱的
I love you, sweetheart.
快点  你都在里面
Hurry up, you've been in there
呆了一个小时了
an hour!
等一下  小麻烦
One second, Maggot!
该死
Oh, fuck.
有人吗
Hello?
妈妈
Hey Mom.
我们到了你和爸爸最喜欢的地方了
We made it to you and Dad's favorite spot.
我想你
Miss you.
你还好吗
You okay?
我很好
\ I'm good.
帮我来做晚餐吗
Help me make dinner?
没问题  等我一会儿
Sure, in a second.
好的
Okay.
你是电影里的角色吗
Are you in a movie?
是
Un huh
你是女人吗
Are you a woman?
不是
No.
等等
Wait.
不是
No.
你是人类吗
Are you human?
不是
Nope.
你是机器人吗
Are you a robot?
是
Yes.
你最好的朋友是机器人吗
Is your best friend a robot?
也许是
Maybe.
你最好的朋友
Does your best friend
对你指手画脚吗
boss you around?
- 没错  - 老天爷
\ Yep. \ Oh my God.
直接说出来吧
Just say it already!
你是不是
Are you...
R2D2
R2\D2?
爸爸又赢了
Dad wins once again!
真吃惊
Shocker...
你之所以会这么刻薄
Ah, you're just bitter
是因为你来大姨妈了
'cause you're on your period.
行啦
All right.
天呐  真搞不明白
Oh God, I don't know
你和妈妈是怎么受得了待在这外面的
how you and Mom could stand it out here.
六月份就已经要冻死了
It's freezing and it's June.
这个嘛
Well...
我们有彼此
We had each other
互相依偎在一起
and we snuggled.
- 老爸  - 咋了
- hey,dad?  - hm?
我能闻一下你的啤酒吗
Can I smell your beer?
你能闻一下我的啤酒吗
Can you smell my beer?
别激动  我就是好奇它的味道
Don't get excited, I'm just curious.
闻着像克莱尔
It smells like Claire.
闭嘴吧  小麻烦
Shut up, Maggot.
嘿  茜茜
Hey Sissy?
怎么了  内森
Nathan?
你在写什么
What you writing?
也许是在给她愚蠢的男朋友写信
Probably a letter to her stupid boyfriend.
你生来就是为了
Were you put on this earth
逼我去自杀的吗
to make me wanna kill myself?
如果是这样的话  你会自杀吗
If I was, would you do it?
是不是过了你的睡觉时间了
Isn't it past your bedtime?
我才没有睡觉时间  是不是过了你的睡觉时间了
I don't have a bedtime. Isn't it past your bedtime?
不  你有的  我没有睡觉时间
Yeah, you do,No, 'cause I don't have one.
我没有睡觉时间
I don't have a bedtime.
不  你有的
Yes you do!
- 不  我没有  - 住手
- Yes-- no I don't!  - Don't!
我没有睡觉时间  你就承认吧
I don't have a bedtime, you admit it!
所以说  这个男生
So this boy.
他很特别吗
Is he special?
对我来说  他很特别
To me he is, yeah.
那你怎么不带来让我们见见
Then why haven't we met him?
因为我不想让他讨厌我
Because I want him to like me.
扎心啊
Ouch.
怎么了
What?
我的嘴唇很干  但是我没有带唇膏
My lips are dry and I don't have any chapstick.
你妈妈和她的那些口红
Your mom and her lipstick.
我不知道你还记不记得
I don't know if you remember.
你那时候还小
You were little.
但你经常和你妈妈坐在一起
But you used to sit with your mom,
你们俩坐在镜子前面
both of you plopped down in front of the mirror,
然后一起化妆
and you guys would put on your makeup together.
我记得
Yeah, I remember.
妈妈看起来好漂亮
Mom looked so beautiful.
而我
And...
看起来像个小丑
I looked like a clown.
可爱的小丑
Cute clown.
老妈是个大美人儿
Mom was gorgeous.
没错
Yes, she was.
克莱尔
Claire!
小丫头
Sissy.
走开
Get the fuck off me.
我不是故意让她死的  克莱尔
I didn't want to let her go, Claire.
你得明白这一点
You have to know that.
我不想讨论这件事
I don't wanna talk about this.
你怎么知道
How do you know
没有拯救她的办法了
that there's no way to save her?
- 你怎么知道的  - 那是我做过的
- how do you know that?  - It was the hardest decision
最艰难的决定
I've ever had to make
知道你们姐妹俩
knowing that you two girls--
我说了我不想
I said that I don't want
讨论这件事
to talk about this.
你不是上帝  内森
You're not God, Nathan!
你只是杀死她的凶手
You're just the one who's killing her!
克莱尔
Claire.
我们必须谈谈这件事
We have to talk about it.
她当时非常痛苦  亲爱的
She was in so much pain, honey.
这不是这次旅行的
That's not what this trip
目的
is about.
我只是想让你
I just want you to...
亲爱的  别进去
Sweetheart, don't go inside.
克莱尔
Hey Claire.
Claire!
我不知道该怎么办了  瓦尔
I don't know how to fix this, Val.
茜茜
Sissy?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
亲爱的
Honey?
你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
嘘  没事的
Hey, shh, it's okay.
来吧  躺下来
Come on, let's lie down.
你没事了  来吧
You're okay. Come on.
你怎么了  亲爱的
What is it, honey?
有人  有人在房顶上
There's somebody-- there's someone on the roof!
- 什么  - 我看见了一个人
- What?  - I saw someone.
我看见了一个人  就在
I saw someone just--
刚才在房
Just now on the...
什么
What?
- 宝贝  没有人能爬到那上面去的  - 什么
- Baby, nobody can get up there. - What--
老爸
Dad?
- 这是怎么回事  - 我不知道
\ What is that?  - I don't know.
过来坐到你姐姐旁边
Come over and sit down next to your sissy.
是谁
Hello?
我们有枪
We've got a gun in here.
请让我们进去
Please let us in.
谁在外面
Who's out there?
老爸
Dad?
没关系  亲爱的  没事的
It's okay, honey, all right?
天呐
Jesus.
请你把门打开好吗
Please will you open the door?
你有什么事
What's the problem?
我们想给你看个东西
We want to show you something.
他们真的好奇怪
They look really weird.
别开门
Don't.
万一他们真的需要帮助呢
What if they really need help?
闭嘴  玛姬
Shut up, Maggie!
别  别开门
Don't... don't open it.
我在加油站看见她了
I saw her at the gas station.
我觉得她是跟踪我们过来的
I think that she followed us.
那儿距这里有50英里
That was like 50 miles back!
听着
Listen, um...
我们不能让你进去
We can't let you in.
你知道的  现在太晚了
You know, it's late.
如果你们想打电话
If you guys need a phone,
最好到高速公路上
uh, you might want to make your way up to the highway.
我们迟早会让你们出来
We'll make you come out eventually.
那是绝对不可能的
That's not gonna happen.
三只瞎眼的老鼠
Three blind mice
看他们往哪儿跑
See how they run
我觉得他们走了
I think they're gone.
这可不一定
You don't know that.
只是几个孩子而已
It's just kids.
闭嘴  你个小
Shut up, you little--
- 喂  克莱尔  - 怎么了
\ Hey, Claire!  - What?
你非要把我们带到这里
You dragged us all the way out here,
现在我们困在荒郊野外
and now we're stuck in the middle of nowhere
谁知道外面有什么
with who knows what outside.
你知道吗
Just so you know,
没有人想参加这次旅行
nobody wanted to go on this trip.
克莱尔  这次旅行是为了妈妈
Claire, this trip was for Mom.
是的  但你知道吗
Right, well, guess what?
妈妈已经死了
Mom's dead.
玛姬  这下好了
Mags-- real nice.
嘿  玛姬
Hey Mags.
亲爱的
Honey.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
我要去确定一下他们走了
I'm gonna go make sure they're gone.
- 不要去  - 你不如
- Don't go  - Why don't you go
过去向你妹妹道个歉
back there and apologize to your sister?
玛姬  你能出来吗
Maggie, can you come out?
玛姬
Maggie...
走开
Go away!
嘿
Hey!
玛姬  对不起
Maggie, I'm sorry.
玛姬
Maggie.
我觉得他们走了
Think they're gone.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好了  孩子们
All right, guys.
但愿我们把他们吓跑了
Hopefully we scared 'em off.
回床上继续睡觉吧
Let's go back to bed.
回去  不
There? No.
绝对不行
No way.
那你想睡这张床吗
Do you want to take the bunk?
那你呢
What about you?
我要继续守着你们
I am gonna keep watch.
以防那帮混蛋又来敲门
in case those punks come knocking again.
我们会把他们打得满地找牙
We'll give 'em a mouthful of teeth.
休息吧
Get some rest.
明天是个大日子  好吗
Tomorrow's a big day, okay?
好吧
All right.
嘿  克莱尔
Hey, Claire.
嘘
Shh.
起来吧
Come on.
没关系  来吧
It's okay, come on.
是那些孩子干的吗
The kids?
还能是谁
Who else?
- 他妈的  - 不许说脏话
- Fuck! - Watch your mouth.
好吧
All right.
这儿距离高速路只有几英里
Highway's just a few miles back.
只要我找到信号  我就打电话求救
Soon as I get reception I'll call for help
或者在马路上拦下别人
or I'll flag somebody down.
你要把我们留在这里
You're leaving us here?
玛姬没法走那么远
Mags can't make that hike.
不要把车的事告诉她
And don't tell her about the truck.
但愿在她醒来之前我就能回来了
Hopefully I'll be back before she wakes up.
嘿
Hey.
我需要你在这儿陪着你妹妹
I need you to stay here with your sister.
如果他们回来怎么办
What if they come back?
那就跑到拖车里面
You're gonna get in that trailer
把门锁上  在我回来之前  你们要
and you're gonna lock the door and you're gonna stay in there
一直待在里面
till I get back.
他们来敲门
咚咚  是谁在那
黑眼珠的孩子  在你巢穴
他们在夜晚潜伏  寻找不幸
像小偷一样窃取灵魂
但他们会预先发出警告  一旦被拒绝
他们便会将你诱出来  这便是他们的把戏
佚名
失踪人口
我受不了了
好了宝贝  我保证
嘿  妈妈
你过得怎么样  我们在路上不知道走了多长时间
爸爸做主 我快冻死了
我现在很迷茫
整段旅程都很压抑  真希望你在这
如果这次旅行能让你回到我身边哪怕只有一天
我也认了
我想你妈妈
救救我
我们能进去吗
好吗
Okay?
1  1  1  1  1
One, one, one, one, one.
给你
Okay.
好了  你们俩待在拖车里面
All right, you guys just stay in the trailer.
我会在早餐前回来的  好吗
I'll be back before breakfast, okay?
嘿
Uh, hey?
怎么了
What is it?
没什么
Um, it's, uh, nothing.
- 你确定吗  - 是的
\ You sure?  - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
你在干嘛呢
What are you doin'?
不关你的事
None of your business.
告诉你男朋友
Telling your boyfriend
没有他你活不下去吗
you can't live without him?
你有何贵干
What do you want?
老爸呢
Where's Dad?
他去远足了
Uh, he went for a hike.
他说他会在早餐前回来
He said he'll be back for breakfast.
可我现在饿了
Well, I'm hungry now.
他为什么不叫醒我
And why didn't he wake me up?
我会和他一起去的
I would have gone with him.
他说他要你待在这
\ He said that he wanted you to stay here,
他说了算
and he's the boss, so...
出什么事了你不告诉我
Something's going on you're not telling me.
我不是小孩了
I'm not a kid.
可你就是
Yes, you are...
小屁孩
a kid.
你要不用步话机联系一下他
Okay, do you want to try him on the walkie?
好
Yeah.
这样
Just...
爸爸  你能听到吗  完毕
Dad, do you read? Over.
我是玛姬
It's Maggie.
再说一遍完毕试试
Try saying "over" again.
我是玛姬  完毕
It's Maggie. Over.
他怎么不回答
Why isn't he answering?
你在吗  完毕
You there? Over.
一定是超出距离了
Uh, he must be out of range.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
要是他迷路了怎么办
What if he got lost?
或者失足跌落了
Or fell?
或者被蛇咬了
Or got bit by a snake?
你知不知道响尾蛇能在一秒之内
Did you know rattlesnakes can strike up to three meters
扑向三米以外的地方吗
in under one second?
- 玛姬  - 那比爸爸的
\ Maggie \ That's way faster
反应速度要快多了
than Dad can even move.
玛姬
Maggie, it...
不会有事的  好嘛
It'll be fine, okay?
去把衣服换了
Just go and get dressed.
内森  你在吗
Nathan, you there?
还在担心吗
Still worried?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
他很快会回来了
He'll be back soon.
能让我玩玩嘛
Can I play?
这不是玩具
It's not a toy.
没有妈妈的娃娃
No figure of Mom, huh?
做得很不错
It's really nice.
你真这么觉得
You think so?
你一直都带在身边吗
Do you keep it with you all the time?
是  怎么了
Yeah, so?
我觉得这样很聪明
I think that's really smart.
这样妈妈就能一直守护你了
That way Mom can always look out for you.
想来帮我做条狗放在院子里吗
Want to help me make a dog house for the yard?
我们没养狗
We don't have a dog.
有点梦想又不为过
No, but a girl can dream.
好吧
Okay.
狗的脸做好了
Made the dog's face so far.
狗是蓝色的
The dog's blue.
- 没错  - 好的
\ Yeah. \ Okay.
喂
Hello?
玛姬  你饿了吗
Maggie, getting hungry?
玛姬
Maggie?
玛姬  你在哪
Maggie, where are you?
玛姬
Maggie?
见鬼
Shit.
玛姬  这样不好玩
Maggie, this isn't funny.
玛姬
Maggie?
该死
Fuck.
玛姬
Maggie?
有人吗
Hello?
玛姬
Maggie?
谁在那
Who's out there?
请让我们进去
Please let us in.
我们这里有枪
We've got a gun in here.
你能不能 把门打开
Please will you open the door?
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
我们迟早会让你出来
We'll make you come out eventually.
克莱尔
Claire?
克莱尔  你能听到我说话吗
Claire, do you hear me?
嘘  小宝贝
Hush, little baby
别说话
Don't say a word
妈妈去给你买只知更鸟
Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
玛姬
Maggie?
- 玛姬  - 别唱歌
\ Maggie. - Don't sing
妈妈去给你买一只知更鸟
Mama's gonna buy you a diamond ring
玛姬
Maggie?
有人吗
Hello?
克莱尔
Claire!
摇啊摇  小宝贝
Rock\a\bye, baby
On the treetop
再高高的树上
When the wind blows
摇篮摇啊摇
The cradle will rock
克莱尔
Claire?
玛姬
Maggie?
克莱尔
Claire!
摇下一个小宝宝
And down will come baby
你想让我回来
You wanted me back.
我回来了
Now here I am.
到妈妈这来
Come to Mommy.
救命
Help!
内森
Nathan!
救命
Help!
内森
Nathan!
克莱尔
Claire!
救命
Help!
过来   过来
Hey, come here, come here.
没事了  没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
那里面有东西
There's something in there.
看起来像是妈妈
It looked like it was Mom,
而且
and...
我想我要疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
我正在  正在  找玛姬
I was\\ I was just\\ I was looking for Maggie,
- 因为她  - 玛姬
- because she \ Maggie?
-她离开了  - 玛姬在哪
\ She left the \ Where's Maggie?
- 她离开了拖车  -玛姬在哪  克莱尔
\ She left the trailer and I \ Where's Maggie, Claire?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know, I mean, I don't know, she\\
你是哦不知道是什么意思
What do you mean you don't know?
玛姬
Maggie!
玛姬  宝贝
Maggie, baby!
玛姬
Maggie!
- 玛姬  - 爸爸
\ Maggie? - Dad.
你上哪去了
Where the fuck were you?
别爆粗口
Stop cussing.
过来  过来
Come here, come here.
我以为听到你在外面
I thought I heard you
我就出来了
outside and I went out there.
然后我的一个娃娃就不见了
And I lost one of my figures.
听着  你不能离开拖车
Listen, you cannot leave this trailer.
我走了之后  克莱尔佐助
When I'm gone, Claire's in charge.
你听明白了吗
Do you understand?
这是你的娃娃
Here's your doll.
你保证过永远不会离开我
You said you'd never leave me, you promised.
玛姬  我会回来的
Maggie, I was coming back.
我只想找信号
I was just trying to go find signal.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
听着  除非你和我一起否则你不能离开拖车
Listen, you cannot leave this trailer unless you're with me.
这对你们俩都一样
That goes for both of you.
我们现在该怎么办
What do we do now?
我们不能离开
We can't leave.
卡车打不着
Truck won't start.
我们今晚在这过夜
So, we'll stay here tonight.
明天一早
And then tomorrow morning,
我们所有人一起走到公路上
all of us will hike up to the road.
跟妈妈告别怎么办
What about saying goodbye to Mom?
她得等等了
She's gonna have to wait.
我今天出去的时候
When I went on the hike earlier today,
发现一辆拖车
I found a trailer
里面有一个男人的尸体
and there was a dead man inside of it.
他怎么了
What happened to him?
他自杀了
He, uh, he killed himself.
我觉得是那些孩子干的
But I think those kids made him do it.
好像是他们在外面守着等他出去
It's like they were daring him to go outside.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
我不知道
I don't know.
你为什么跑到垃圾场里去了
What made you go to the junkyard?
玛姬不见了  我在那里听到了她的声音
Maggie was missing and I heard her voice up there.
我找到了她的娃娃
I found her doll.
我不明白是怎么回事
I don't understand what's going on.
我想他们是想把我们引出去
I think they're trying to lure us out.
如果他们今晚来敲门
If they come knocking again tonight,
你们别离开拖车
you two do not leave this trailer.
不管发生什么
No matter what.
你在准备什么
What you workin' on?
派对
A party.
是吗
Oh yeah?
什么样的派对
What kind of party?
给妈妈准备的欢迎派对
A welcome home party for Mom.
这里是什么
What do we have here?
她一定会喜欢的
Oh, yeah, she'd love that.
这些是灯吗
Are they the lights?
是粉色的  我觉得她会喜欢的
It's pink, I thought she would like it.
你觉得不觉得有点太闪了
Do you think these are too sparkly?
彩灯不是多多益善吗
Is there a such thing as too sparkly?
这是个惊喜  所以把什么都别说了
And it's a surprise, so don't say anything.
快到睡觉时间了
It's almost bed time.
我们收拾一下明天再做
Can we clean this up and finish tomorrow?
好的
Okay.
带上玛姬  去厕所躲着
Grab Maggie, go to the bathroom,
呆在那别动
stay there.
爸爸
Dad?
和你姐姐回去呆着
You go back with your sister,
我马上就回来
and I'll be right back, okay?
你保证吗
Promise?
我保证
Promise.
把门锁上
Lock the door.
快来
Okay, come on.
爸爸没事吧
\ Is Dad okay?
我们有枪
We've got a gun!
如果你们再不停下来
If you guys don't quit messing around,
就有人要没命了
somebody's gonna get killed.
你愿意和我玩吗
Will you play with me?
你伤了我
You hurt me.
他怎么花了这么久
What's taking him so long?
好吧
Okay.
让我进去
Just let me in.
不
No!
克莱尔
Claire.
克莱尔  你能听到我吗
Claire, can you hear me?
克莱尔
Claire?
能听到  我们在呢
Yeah, yeah, we're here.
你们没事吧
Are you guys okay?
差不多吧
Kind of, yeah.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
差不多吧
Kind of.
我被困在车里了  但我没事
I'm trapped in the truck, but I'm okay.
听着  我还是不知道他们想干嘛
Listen, I still don't know what they want,
但除非你邀请他们  否则他们进不去  好吗
but they can't come in unless you invite them, okay?
-  不  不  不   - 老爸
\ No, no, no.  - Dad!
-  我们听不清楚  - 老爸
\ We can't hear you.  - Dad!
待在原地不要动
Just stay put.
喂
Hello?
克莱尔
Claire?
他为什么不回答
Why isn't he answering?
等等  你待在这里
Hang on, just stay here.
什么  不行
What? No!
- 把门锁上  - 不  不要走
- Lock the door. - No, don't go!
我得到接收范围内
I just-- I have to get within range,
我马上就回来  我保证
I'll be right back, I promise.
就两分钟  两分钟后就回来
Two minutes, give me two minutes.
克莱尔  你能听到吗
Claire, can you hear me?
你能听到吗
Can you hear me?
克莱尔
Claire?
内森
Nathan?
Nathan.
内森
你能听到我声音吗  内森
Can you hear me, Nathan?
内森
Nathan?
克莱尔
Claire.
让我进去吧
Just let me in.
妈妈
Mommy!
玛姬
Maggie.
你为什么做不到呢
Why can't you do it?
为什么
Why?
你真是太自私了
You're so fucking selfish.
离我们远点儿
Stay the fuck away from us!
你甚至都没法保护我们的孩子
You can't even protect our babies.
那不是瓦尔
That's not Val.
我能进来吗
Can I come in?
离我们远点儿
Leave us alone!
那不是瓦尔
That's not Val.
拜托  拜托
Come on, come on.
怎么了  玛姬小熊熊
What's the matter, Maggie bear?
你不想和妈妈一起玩儿吗
Don't you want to play with mama?
你没有疯
You are not going crazy.
不
No.
你不是真的
You're not real!
因为你我才会死
You are the reason I'm dead.
真的是你吗  妈妈
Is it really you, Mommy?
当然是我了  宝贝
Of course it's me, baby.
克莱尔
Claire?
嘿  克莱尔  你能听到我声音吗
Hey, Claire-- Can you hear me?
我爱你
I love you.
我还以为你永远离开了
I thought you were gone forever.
- 你为什么要离开我们  - 玛姬
- Why did you leave us? - Maggie?
妈妈  我想死你了
Oh, Mommy, I missed you!
我就在这里
I'm right here.
玛姬  你在和谁说话
Maggie, who are you talking to?
克莱尔  你能听到我声音吗
Claire, can you hear me?
让我进去吧  亲爱的
Just let me in, my love.
克莱尔
Claire.
Claire?
玛姬
Maggie.
玛姬  把门打开
Maggie, open the door.
玛姬
Maggie.
玛姬  把门打开
Maggie, open the door!
玛姬
Maggie!
嘿  你们几个小混蛋
Hey, you little motherfuckers.
来啊
Come on.
想和我玩儿
You wanna play?
来啊  上啊
Come on in, come on!
把门打开  克莱尔
Unlock the door, Claire!
快点  宝贝
Come on, baby.
没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
玛姬  玛姬呢
Maggie? Where's Maggie?
她在浴缸里
She's in the tub.
她在浴缸里  她死了
She's in the tub, she's dead.
- 什么  - 她死了
- What? - She's dead.
玛姬
Maggie?
出来  亲爱的
Come on out, honey.
玛姬
Maggie!
亲爱的
Honey?
她刚刚就在这里
She was right here.
我看见她的尸体了
I saw her body.
他们就想让你
That's what they want
这么认为  亲爱的
you to think, honey.
玛姬
Maggie!
他们的目标是小孩子们
They're after the kids.
从来都和我们没关系
Never had anything to do with us.
- 什么  - 过来
- What?  - Come on.
- 干嘛  - 他们的目标不是我们
- What?  - It was never about us.
他们一直想抓走玛姬
They wanted Maggie all along.
过来
Come on.
玛姬
Maggie?
Maggie!
克莱尔  快来
Claire, come on!
玛姬
Maggie!
但我看到了妈妈
But I saw Mom.
我也看到了妈妈
I saw Mom, too.
不只是这样
It's not just that.
玛姬  我在门外听见她在说话
Maggie, I heard her talking to her through the door.
这是他们耍的把戏  亲爱的
It's just games they're playing with us, honey.
好了  听我说
Okay, listen!
我觉得她想告诉我们什么
I think she's trying to tell us something.
- 你带着这个干嘛  - 我也不知道  我只是
\ Why'd you bring this?  - I don't know, I just--
过来啊  老爸
Come on, Daddy!
玛姬
Maggie!
- 玛姬  - 来啊  爸爸
- Maggie!  - Come on, Daddy!
- 我在这儿  爸爸  - 亲爱的
- I'm over here, Daddy! - Honey?
你永远都抓不到我
You'll never catch me!
玛姬
Maggie?
Maggie!
爸爸  过来抓我啊
Daddy, come get me!
你永远都抓不到我
You'll never catch me!
玛姬
Maggie?
- 来吧  - 我不过去
\ Come on.  - I can't.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
好吧  我马上回来
Okay, I'll be right back.
内森
Nathan?
克莱尔
Claire?
玛姬
Maggie?
你来了
You're here.
你回来找我了
You came back for me.
你不是真的
You're not real.
玛姬呢
Where's Maggie?
她在这儿
She's here.
她很安全
She's safe.
为什么
Why?
你背叛了我们
You betrayed us.
背叛了家人
Our family.
背叛了我
Me.
你任我死去
You let me die.
- 为什么要这么做  内森  - 瓦尔
\ Why, Nate?  - Oh, Val.
你那时非常痛苦
You were suffering.
你放弃了
You gave up.
现在你想丢掉和我的回忆
And now you're trying to throw my memory away.
不
No.
我不想的
I don't want to.
你不用丢掉的
You don't have to.
我们可以重新在一起
We can be together again.
我们可以重新成为家人
We can be a family again.
留在这儿陪我
Stay here with me.
内森
Nathan...
我不想让你担心我
I don't want you to worry about me.
照顾好彼此
Take care of each other.
内森
Nathan!
答应我
Promise me,
等到合适的时机
when the time is right,
让我离开吧
you'll let me go.
你不是我的瓦尔
You're not my Val.
我的瓦尔已经死了
My Valerie's gone.
内森
Nathan!
- 嘿  - 是克莱尔
- Hey.  - That's Claire.
内森
Nathan!
不  不  不
No, no, no!
克莱尔
Claire?
把瓶子扔给我  克莱尔
Throw me the bottle, Claire!
爸爸
Dad!
让我走吧
You have to let me go.
照顾好彼此
Take care of each other.
你要做什么
What are you doing?
做我们来这儿要做的事
What we came here to do.
玛姬
Maggie.
快走
Come on.
- 玛姬  - 爸爸
- Maggie... - Daddy!
没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
爸爸  他们抓走了我
Daddy, they got me!
过来让我看看
Here, let me see.
- 你没事吧  - 我看见妈妈了
- You okay? - I saw Mommy.
她就在那里  就在拖车外面
She was there, she was outside of the trailer,
我看见她了  她让我跟她走  我照做了
I saw her, and she told me to come with her and I did.
不  那不是妈妈
No, that wasn't Mommy.
我好害怕啊  老爸
I was so scared, Daddy.
我明白
I know.
嘘  但你现在没事了
Shh, but you're okay.
你没事了  我们在一起
You're okay, we're together.
没事了
It's okay.
下次如果去旅行的话
Next time we go on a trip,
我们不能住在酒店里吗
can we just stay in a hotel?
你知道结局是什么*
* You know how it is at the end
你在考虑这是怎么开始的*
* You start to consider the beginning
那些改变了的人*
* All those faces that change
想把你卷进去*
* Trying to reel you in
你眼中的爱人*
* The lover in your eyes
想把你带回过去*
* Keeps drawing you back to place
这是她最想做的事*
* It was her favorite thing
现在我已记不起她的脸庞*
* Now I can't quite place her face
我不想说这是对的*
* I don't wanna say right
但这也不是错的*
* Don't wanna say wrong
他已经离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝  离开了*
* He's gone, baby, gone, baby, gone, baby, gone
离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝*
* Gone, baby, gone, baby, gone, baby
离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝  离开了*
* Gone, baby, gone, baby, gone, baby, gone
离开了  宝贝  离开了  宝贝  离开了*
* Gone, baby, gone, baby, gone
翻译   Lysenko
翻译   文睿君
翻译   不会吐泡泡的金鱼
翻译   灯灯
翻译   凉席
校对   lysenko
统筹   Kate
片源   耐了个卡卡
黑暗诗选
第一季   第九章
m -30 -8 l -29 -9 l -26 -11 l -24 -12 l -26 -14 l -28 -15 l -28 -16 l -25 -17 l -22 -17 l -22 -18 l -21 -18 l -20 -20 l -18 -20 l -16 -18 l -6 -18 l -5 -17 l -5 -12 l -6 -11 l -7 -11 l -7 -16 l -18 -16 l -19 -18 l -19 -17 l -21 -17 l -21 -15 l -22 -15 l -23 -15 l -25 -15 l -23 -13 l -23 -12 l -25 -10 l -27 -9 l -27 -8 l -23 -7 l -21 -4 l -21 -3 l -23 0 l -26 4 l -27 9 l -26 12 l -24 13 l -14 13 l -14 11 l -14 7 l -13 5 l -12 3 l -9 -1 l -7 -2 l -14 -2 l -14 1 l -15 4 l -17 5 l -19 4 l -18 3 l -17 3 l -16 1 l -16 -2 l -16 -3 l -8 -3 l -6 -3 l -5 -3 l -3 -4 l -1 -4 l -3 -5 l -4 -8 l -4 -17 l -4 -18 l -2 -18 l -2 -8 l -1 -6 l 1 -5 l 4 -5 l 6 -7 l 6 -16 l 5 -18 l 8 -18 l 9 -17 l 8 -16 l 8 -8 l 6 -5 l 4 -4 l 5 -4 l 7 -2 l 12 -4 l 12 -16 l 11 -18 l 14 -18 l 22 -7 l 22 -16 l 21 -17 l 21 -19 l 21 -20 l 22 -21 l 23 -20 l 24 -18 l 24 -16 l 25 -16 l 26 -15 l 26 -9 l 26 -8 l 25 -7 l 24 -7 l 24 -4 l 22 -4 l 14 -15 l 14 -10 l 14 -4 l 13 -4 l 7 0 l 6 2 l 4 4 l 1 4 l 3 3 l 5 2 l 6 -2 l 4 -3 l 1 -3 l 0 -1 l 0 0 l 1 1 l 3 2 l 1 2 l -1 1 l -1 -1 l -3 -3 l -4 -2 l -5 -1 l -5 2 l -4 3 l -1 3 l 2 3 l 0 4 l -3 4 l -5 4 l -6 2 l -6 -1 l -8 0 l -10 3 l -12 7 l -12 11 l -11 13 l -12 14 l -26 14 l -28 13 l -29 11 l -29 8 l -28 5 l -27 2 l -25 0 l -24 -2 l -23 -4 l -24 -6 l -28 -7 l -30 -8 m -17 -15 l -16 -15 l -13 -11 l -10 -15 l -8 -15 l -12 -10 l -8 -4 l -10 -4 l -12 -8 l -13 -8 l -14 -6 l -15 -4 l -16 -4 l -17 -4 l -14 -9 l -14 -10 l -17 -14 l -18 -15
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
翻译
m 0 0 b 0 5 0 9 0 14 b -1 15 -1 16 -2 17 b -4 17 -7 17 -9 17 b -9 14 -9 11 -9 8 b -9 5 -9 3 -9 0 b -9 -2 -9 -5 -9 -7 b -7 -7 -5 -7 -3 -7 b -3 -7 -3 -6 -3 -6 b -3 -6 -3 -5 -3 -5 b -4 -5 -6 -5 -7 -5 b -7 -3 -7 -1 -7 1 b -7 6 -7 10 -7 15 b -6 15 -4 15 -3 15 b -3 11 -3 7 -3 3 b -3 -1 -3 -5 -3 -9 b -3 -9 -3 -9 -3 -9 b -5 -9 -7 -9 -9 -9 b -9 -10 -9 -10 -9 -11 b -7 -11 -5 -11 -3 -11 b -3 -13 -3 -16 -3 -18 b -2 -18 0 -17 1 -17 b 1 -17 0 -16 0 -16 b 0 -14 0 -13 0 -11 b 1 -11 2 -11 3 -11 b 3 -11 3 -10 3 -10 b 2 -10 1 -10 0 -10 b 0 -9 0 -8 0 -7 b 3 -7 5 -7 8 -7 b 8 -10 8 -13 8 -16 b 8 -16 7 -16 7 -16 b 7 -17 8 -17 8 -18 b 9 -18 10 -17 11 -17 b 11 -15 11 -13 11 -11 b 18 -11 26 -11 33 -11 b 33 -11 32 -10 32 -10 b 25 -10 18 -10 11 -10 b 11 -9 11 -8 11 -7 b 18 -7 26 -7 33 -7 b 33 -7 33 -6 33 -6 b 26 -6 18 -6 11 -6 b 11 -5 11 -5 11 -4 b 11 -4 11 -3 11 -3 b 17 -3 24 -3 30 -3 b 31 -3 31 -2 32 -2 b 32 -2 33 -1 33 -1 b 33 -1 34 0 34 0 b 34 1 33 1 33 2 b 32 3 32 3 31 4 b 27 4 22 4 18 4 b 23 8 29 11 34 15 b 34 16 34 16 34 17 b 33 17 33 17 32 17 b 27 14 22 10 17 7 b 16 6 16 6 15 5 b 15 4 15 4 15 3 b 16 3 16 2 17 2 b 21 2 26 2 30 2 b 30 1 31 1 31 0 b 31 0 30 -1 30 -1 b 30 -1 29 -2 29 -2 b 23 -2 17 -2 11 -2 b 11 4 11 11 11 17 b 10 17 9 17 8 17 b 8 9 8 2 8 -6 b 5 -6 3 -6 0 -6 b 0 -4 0 -2 0 0 b -3 6 -7 11 -10 17 b -11 17 -12 17 -13 17 b -13 9 -13 2 -13 -6 b -13 -6 -14 -7 -14 -7 b -14 -7 -14 -6 -14 -6 b -14 1 -14 8 -14 15 b -15 15 -16 15 -17 15 b -17 8 -17 1 -17 -6 b -17 -6 -18 -6 -18 -6 b -18 1 -18 8 -18 15 b -19 15 -20 15 -21 15 b -21 8 -21 1 -21 -6 b -21 -6 -22 -6 -22 -6 b -22 2 -22 9 -22 17 b -23 17 -24 17 -25 17 b -25 9 -25 0 -25 -8 b -23 -8 -22 -8 -20 -8 b -20 -10 -19 -12 -19 -14 b -21 -14 -23 -14 -25 -14 b -25 -15 -25 -15 -25 -16 b -20 -16 -14 -16 -9 -16 b -9 -16 -9 -15 -9 -15 b -9 -15 -9 -14 -9 -14 b -11 -14 -13 -14 -15 -14 b -16 -12 -16 -10 -17 -8 b -15 -8 -12 -8 -10 -8 b -10 -3 -10 2 -10 7 b -10 10 -10 14 -10 17
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177